<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<!-- SCPs -->
	<LetterSCP939Enters>SCP939</LetterSCP939Enters>
	<LetterSCP939EntersText>A pack of SCP939 have been spotted near the area. Be on the lookout.
		
	While they may not enter the area immediately, they may wander in and hunt any humanoids in the vicinity.
	</LetterSCP939EntersText>

	<!-- Letter Incidents -->
	<LetterLabelContainmentBreach>Containment Breach</LetterLabelContainmentBreach>
	<LetterContainmentBreach>One or more SCPs are trying to escape containment!\n\nStop their advances or destroy them.</LetterContainmentBreach>
	<LetterLabelSCP3199Attack>SCP-3199 Invasion</LetterLabelSCP3199Attack>
	<LetterSCP3199Attack>A flock of SCP-3199 have appeared.\n\nContain or kill them.\n\nThey will probably leave the area in a few days, leaving a LOT of eggs behind.\n\nDon't wait to get rid of the eggs, they will quickly spiral out of control.</LetterSCP3199Attack>
	<MBReason>The final straw was: </MBReason>
	<LetterLabelSCP131Join>SCP-131s join</LetterLabelSCP131Join>
	<LetterSCP131Join>A pair of SCP-131s, abandoned or lost, have wandered into the area.\n\nThey seem to adore human contact and are joining the colony.</LetterSCP131Join>
	<LetterLabelSCP529Join>SCP-529 join</LetterLabelSCP529Join>
	<LetterSCP529Join>A female SCP-529, abandoned or lost, have wandered into the area.\n\nThey seem to adore human contact and are joining the colony.</LetterSCP529Join>
	<LetterLabelSCP610Local>SCP-610 formation</LetterLabelSCP610Local>
	<LetterSCP610Local>A few SCP-610 instances formed nearby.</LetterSCP610Local>
	<LetterLabelSCP2845Attack>SCP-2845 Invasion</LetterLabelSCP2845Attack>
	<LetterSCP2845Attack>An SCP-2845 and its SCP-2845-1 minions have appeared.\n\nContain or kill them.\n\nThey will probably leave the area in a few days.</LetterSCP2845Attack>

	<!-- Specific SCP -->
	<SCP113>SCP-113 changed the pawn's gender to </SCP113>
	<SCP113F>nothing happened.</SCP113F>

	<!-- Containment Procedures -->
	<SCP_Contain>Containment class</SCP_Contain>
	<SCP_Disrupt>Disruption class</SCP_Disrupt>
	<SCP_Risk>Risk class</SCP_Risk>

	<!-- Containment -->
	<SCP_CSafe>Safe</SCP_CSafe>
	<SCP_CSafeDesc>Anomaly that are easily and safely contained.</SCP_CSafeDesc>

	<SCP_CEuclid>Euclid</SCP_CEuclid>
	<SCP_CEuclidDesc>Anomaly require more resources to contain completely or where containment isn't always reliable.</SCP_CEuclidDesc>

	<SCP_CKeter>Keter</SCP_CKeter>
	<SCP_CKeterDesc>Anomaly that is exceedingly difficult to contain consistently or reliably, with containment procedures often being extensive and complex.</SCP_CKeterDesc>

	<SCP_CThaumiel>Thaumiel</SCP_CThaumiel>
	<SCP_CThaumielDesc>Anomaly that can specifically used to contain other SCPs.</SCP_CThaumielDesc>

	<SCP_CApollyon>Apollyon</SCP_CApollyon>
	<SCP_CApollyonDesc>Anomaly that cannot be contained, are expected to breach containment imminently, or some other similar scenario.</SCP_CApollyonDesc>
	
	<SCP_CNeutralized>Neutralized</SCP_CNeutralized>
	<SCP_CNeutralizedDesc>Anomaly has been neutralized.</SCP_CNeutralizedDesc>
	<!-- Disruption -->
	<SCP_DDark>Dark</SCP_DDark>
	<SCP_DDarkDesc>Little to no potential to disrupt the general population.</SCP_DDarkDesc>

	<SCP_DVlam>Vlam</SCP_DVlam>
	<SCP_DVlamDesc>Low potential to disrupt the general population. Disruption is typically confined to a locality.</SCP_DVlamDesc>

	<SCP_DKeneq>Keneq</SCP_DKeneq>
	<SCP_DKeneqDesc>Medium potential to disrupt the general population. Disruption is typically confined to a region or city.</SCP_DKeneqDesc>

	<SCP_DEkhi>Ekhi</SCP_DEkhi>
	<SCP_DEkhiDesc>High potential to disrupt the general population. Disruption is typically widespread, affecting major metropolitan areas or countries.</SCP_DEkhiDesc>

	<!-- Risk -->
	<SCP_RNotice>Notice</SCP_RNotice>
	<SCP_RNoticeDesc>The anomaly in question has a low risk potential. Individuals nearby may feel minimal effects from the anomaly, but these effects rarely pose any harm or even discomfort.</SCP_RNoticeDesc>

	<SCP_RCaution>Caution</SCP_RCaution>
	<SCP_RCautionDesc>The anomaly in question has a moderate risk potential. Individuals nearby will likely experience the effects of the anomaly, and these effects may cause discomfort or harm.</SCP_RCautionDesc>

	<SCP_RWarning>Warning</SCP_RWarning>
	<SCP_RWarningDesc>The anomaly in question has a high risk potential. Individuals nearby will likely experience the acute effects of the anomaly and will be at risk for experiencing severe harm, up to and including death.</SCP_RWarningDesc>

	<SCP_RDanger>Danger</SCP_RDanger>
	<SCP_RDangerDesc>The anomaly in question has a very high risk potential. Individuals nearby will invariably be exposed to harm, up to and including death. These effects are very difficult to mitigate.</SCP_RDangerDesc>

	<SCP_RCritical>Critical</SCP_RCritical>
	<SCP_RCriticalDesc>The anomaly in question has an extremely severe risk potential. Individuals nearby will invariably be exposed to acute, life-threatening harm. These effects cannot be mitigated.</SCP_RCriticalDesc>
	
	<!-- Scranton Reality Anchor -->
	<SCP.Interface.TargetEffect>Target psychic sensitivity decrease: {0}</SCP.Interface.TargetEffect>
    <SCP.Interface.TargetRadius>Target radius: {0}</SCP.Interface.TargetRadius>
    <SCP.Interface.PowerConsumption>Predicted power consumption: {0}W</SCP.Interface.PowerConsumption>
	<SCP.SuppressionField.CurrentEffect>Psychic sensitivity decrease: {0}</SCP.SuppressionField.CurrentEffect>
    <SCP.SuppressionField.CurrentRadius>Current radius: {0}</SCP.SuppressionField.CurrentRadius>
    <SCP.SuppressionField.ConfigureSuppressionField>Configure suppression field</SCP.SuppressionField.ConfigureSuppressionField>
    <SCP.SuppressionField.ConfigureSuppressionFieldDesc>Configure the radius and strength of the suppression</SCP.SuppressionField.ConfigureSuppressionFieldDesc>

	<!-- Containment Zones -->
	<SCP_AssignSCP>Assign SCP(s)</SCP_AssignSCP>
	<SCP_AssignSCPDesc>Assign scp(s) to capture and keep in the cage.</SCP_AssignSCPDesc>

</LanguageData>